Look at the boobs with just your hands.
手だけでおっぱい見してください
Not anymore
もうやね
yeah.
ん
Do you understand?
す っか分かる?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
Where does it hurt?
どこが痛い?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Back?
奥?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
痛 くない?
Have you ever been on top?
上に乗ったことある?
what up?
どうした?
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちよくない?
I don't know.
わかんない
I've never done it.
やったことない
I say it very loudly.
めっちゃポチャポチャ言う
Why don't you bring it out?
出し立ててごらん?
It's very accurate.
めっちゃ当たっている
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I don't know.
わかんない
it hurts.
痛い
It hurts but feels good.
痛い気持ちいい
Does the pain feel good?
痛い気持ちいい?
Can you put your hands behind your back?
手を後ろについてごらん?
yes.
そう
oh yeah.
そうそう
Can be put in and taken out.
出し入れできる
My feet hurt.
足痛い
Can be put in and taken out.
出し入れできる
Can I go from behind next time?
今度後ろから行ってもいい?
Have you ever done that?
したことある?
do not have.
ない
I like the one that sleeps.
寝るやつがいい
I've never done it though.
やったことないけど
what?
何?
Sleeping bag?
寝バック?
Why don't you go to sleep?
寝てごらん?
I don't know how to sleep.
寝方わかんない
Immediately lie down on your stomach.
そんすぐにうつ伏せ
good?
いい?
No?
ダ メ?
good?
いい?
I'll go.
行くよ
Are you almost done?
もうちょい終わった?